Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ chaharnishant11 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

C++

Python (Programming Language) MySQL

Certifications

C++ & Data Structures
Full Stack Web Delevlopment

Nishant Chahar

SDE @ Microsoft | 200k+ Subs on YT | NSIT Delhi, India

Summary

I am a Software Engineer @Microsoft, Graduated from NSIT. I have interned at Samsung Research Institute Bangalore and I have also won SIH'20.

I like to explore new things and in this journey i have a YouTube channel with 100k+ Subscribers.Do check it out!

Experience

Microsoft Software Engineer July 2021 - Present (1 year 3 months) India

YouTube

Digital Creator September 2020 - Present (2 years 1 month)

Crosslinks NSUT

3 years 10 months

President

July 2020 - July 2021 (1 year 1 month)

Executive Committee Member

October 2017 - July 2020 (2 years 10 months)

Executive committee member at Crosslinks, NSUT - The public and student relations society of NSUT.

CodeChef

Educator

May 2021 - June 2021 (2 months)

A.R.E.S. Robotics

1 year 11 months

President

May 2020 - April 2021 (1 year)

Senior Software and Autonomous Traversal Engineer June 2019 - May 2020 (1 year)

Management Lead

June 2019 - May 2020 (1 year)

Management Lead at A.R.E.S. Robotics. I help in keeping coordination between all the departments and take care of the funds for building the rover.

The Alliance - NSIT's Newspaper

3 years 5 months

Managing Editor

December 2019 - February 2021 (1 year 3 months)

Handling all the day to day activities of the society. Managing the workflow and a team of 40 members.

Senior Caricaturist

November 2018 - December 2019 (1 year 2 months)

Caricaturist

October 2017 - November 2018 (1 year 2 months)

Samsung Electronics

Software Engineer Intern

May 2020 - July 2020 (3 months)

Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

Worked in the Network Modem R&D team of SRIB.

Facebook Developer Circle: Delhi-NCR

Study Group Facilitator

July 2019 - March 2020 (9 months)

Coding Ninjas India

Teaching Assistant

June 2019 - October 2019 (5 months)

Delhi, India

Coding Ninjas India

Teaching Assistant October 2018 - January 2019 (4 months) New Delhi Area, India

Education

Netaji Subhas Institute of Technology

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Computer Engineering · (2017 - 2021)